sup everyone came was in the five
through the very special video today and
this is some cool ass [ __ ] that made
it's like my very own one kind Sonic
unbowed on t-shirt and [ __ ] it comes Mac
80 bucks you like making [ __ ] because I
just go to good wear what I got like a
blank and [ __ ] then I got one of my own
but I pics like seats like this one is
like a classic and we true but Arkansan
girlfriend knows that it's like it's why
I'm baby it's mmm it's it's literally
Sonic running over to give Bobby like a
glass wall here while he's like [ __ ]
butt naked and [ __ ] but so about is like
a big fat ass right there I am so gonna
wear this when I go down to dollar
tomorrow to buy some [ __ ] to make some
chili dogs
you'll hearing me I am [ __ ] I'm gonna
do it you can't stop me no one can tell
me what to do I am bi I am well this
[ __ ] yeah I can't believe how cool is it
can you believe I'm wearing this
tomorrow I'm aware of every [ __ ] day
for the rest of my [ __ ] life [ __ ]